sbilife.co.in 2019-05-17

# Privacy Policy

  1. home
  2. privacy policy

##  This policy describes how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our Web site. 

If you visit our site to read or download information, we may collect and/or store the following information about you:

  * the name of the domain from which you access the Internet ;
  * the date and time you accessed our site;
  * the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site;
  * the page locations where you visited, and other miscellaneous site references.

Some pages on this Web site employ "cookies." A cookie is a small file that a Web site transfers to your computer’s hard disk to allow the server to "remember" specific information about your session while you are connected. SBI Life may find it necessary to use the "cookies" system to collect data when you visit our web pages. This will help us find out which sections of our pages you are interested in.

Requests to send cookies are not designed to collect information about you, but only about your "browser session." The cookies make it easier for you to use the dynamic features of our Web site. The cookies and the information about your session are automatically destroyed shortly after you close your browser. The information is not permanently stored on your computer. No personal information about you is collected except as described above.

The primary reason for doing this is to enable SBI Life to appreciate, better, your centres of interest and send you information specific to your requirements. Such data will not be held for more than one year.

This website does not collect any personal information that identifies a visitor to this site individually unless specified otherwise. Your visit to this site will record only the Domain Name Server part of your e-mail address and of the pages visited within this website. The information we receive depends upon what you do when visiting our site. This information is used for management and enhancement of our Web site and also to prepare aggregate information about the visitors to the site and statistics on usage patterns.

If you identify yourself by sending an e-mail or ordering forms/brochures, we will only use this information to respond to your request and improve our Customer Services. Names and addresses are kept in our Customer Services system for 3 months in order to follow up on orders if necessary. They are then deleted from the system.

While every care has been taken in preparing the information and materials contained in this site, such information and materials are provided to you "as is" without warranty of any kind either express or implied. SBI Life does not warranty the adequacy of the information made available. In particular, no warranty regarding non-infringement, security, accuracy, fitness for a particular purpose or freedom from computer virus is given in conjunction with such information and materials. 

##  Cookies 

"Cookies" will also save you from having to supply information that you have previously given, every time you connect. It will be possible for you to detect these "cookies" and, if you wish, delete them.

To do this, we would remind you that your web browser software contains the option of blocking "cookies" on your computer:

  * If your web browser is Internet Explorer 3 or 4 (Microsoft):  
Click on "display", "options", "advanced". Among the various displays you could call up, the fourth is entitled "prompt before accepting cookies" and, on Internet Explorer 4 only, the fifth is entitled "always refuse cookies".
  * If your web browser is Internet Explorer 5 (Microsoft):  
Click on "tools", " internet options ", "security", "custom level". Under the "cookies" heading, select "prompt" or "disable" against the proposed options.
  * If your web browser is Navigator Gold 3 (Netscape):  
Click on "options", "network preferences", "protocols". Among the various prompts that you can activate, the first is entitled "prompt before accepting a cookie". You will then be prompted when a "cookie" arrives and you can have it refused by your browser software.
  * If your web browser is Communicator (Netscape):  
Click on "edit", "preferences" and highlight "advanced". Select the required option.

##  Other web connections: hypertext links 

Our web pages also offer links to other sites for which we are not responsible either for their standards of public order and decency, or for their personal data protection policy or the use that could be made of such data.

When you access another website through a hypertext link, you are accepting that this access is at your own risk. Consequently, SBI Life cannot accept responsibility for any direct or indirect damages that may result from your access to another site connected by a hypertext link.

We would also draw your attention to the use of public forums where you may be asked to give your identity or e-mail address. This information then enters the public domain and may be used by a third party using the service.
